
Speaker 1  (00:02)
This is for my personal. So like they asked me, I can go back because I feel like taking note. Sometimes interrupts the flow of the conversation. 

Speaker 1  (00:09)
So Alright, I think this kind of way. Of starting, everybody's just kind of tell me your thoughts and your processes. And we can just kind of go from there and just hold a conversation and kind of let the flow go 

Speaker 2  (00:23)
So my thoughts on process on 

Speaker 1  (00:26)
So you want to discuss 

Speaker 3  (00:27)
It's probably more like maybe start like your experience with the AI within Kinsey like what you think you said, for today, I mean you could talk about personal too just kind of if you want to talk more about your personal, that's kind of more like your skill set you've built, but just kind of your experience with AI. And then maybe some specifics to Kinsey, to begin 

Speaker 2  (00:44)
Okay, yeah, I would say we Are pretty well on the infant C stage when it comes to AI and the use and concepts of using is primarily around Making jobs easier. A Google search 4.0 I guess a little bit of getting better answers is what I've seen within the company or Building out proof of concept aspects I would say, our greatest limitations are challenges. Are going from? 

Speaker 2  (01:30)
Prove a concept to production Other challenges are skill sets education, quality data. Process consistency. Yep, process consistency, and probably what's prevented us. 

Speaker 2  (01:52)
Moving forward has been around. Probably the coordination or Project management sides of identifying opportunities are a lie and Really? The I'm putting. 

Speaker 2  (02:12)
Any sort of timelines or project aspects on opportunities? It's a lot there to unpack. 

Speaker 3  (02:21)
The good news is, we've unpacked a little bit of it because we've already met with Doug and Steve this morning and met with Jay from the HR compliant side. And then we met with Zach before this. So we talked a little bit on speak too much about mads. 

Speaker 1  (02:36)
No, I think, yeah, that was been the trend of the discussions really 

Speaker 3  (02:40)
That was a good summary. 

Speaker 2  (02:42)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (02:42)
Yeah, that's pretty much our day in. So this came to him, but she did not know it. What are you see from your job? 

Speaker 1  (02:52)
As far as how do you feel? You can move forward using AI. 

Speaker 2  (02:56)
Well, right now I'm working on putting together AI guess. A software. I'm gonna add for competitive pricing. 

Speaker 2  (03:07)
So how I'm currently utilizing AI Primarily is to bet out a data pipeline on extracting text from PDF documents is about the easiest way to get competitor pricing without having to Rebuild. Well how to rebuild, but build out Uh, scraping and the Complexity of getting around robot captures cloud fair flare, other aspects. So the easiest point is just going off a PDF documents on pricing and putting that around text Ryan kind of started that a little bit Perplexity, I've taken that and built out different data pipelines to extract that information put in a repository and then build out a UI layer over top of that with different pricing rules. 

Speaker 2  (04:08)
So from an AI component standpoint on that Um, 2 parts of it building out. Scraping scripts. Yeah, building out pipelines. 

Speaker 2  (04:22)
That way, and then just using AI as software development. I'm not as gonna ask, I'm not a Software Developer, and there's a reason why in my undergraduate, I sweat well, I double majored in Computer Science and business administration, but I pivoted it because my Computer Science background wasn't all accurate sure, so, but that's where it helped. 

Speaker 3  (04:44)
Light level above, say the other average user in terms of 

Speaker 2  (04:47)
Oh, yeah. And then, you know, my experience with an it world, I know, kind of modulizing software development and software development. Life cycle. 

Speaker 2  (04:57)
So it's helpful in that aspect of building out the software I have no idea what codes in the background. I think that conversation I had with Doug is and what I talked about challenges of moving from prototyping or proof of concept to production. Okay, I got this great app that we built, how do we host it? 

Speaker 2  (05:19)
How do we secure it? How do we define access controls? Where do we publish it? 

Speaker 2  (05:24)
All those things that were 

Speaker 3  (05:26)
Yeah, well, we 'Ve been discussing that and I think the consensus is that we have ideas on what standard could end up being, but the intention is that there will be some kind of standard standard process for the testing standard process for the ownership transfer from, let's say the proof of concept towards the enterprise. Release standard process for I'll let you speak to the terminology here. But basically embedding standard pieces within the actual AI side so that we're getting consistency in the code structure. 

Speaker 3  (06:00)
Right? Consistency both in the security structure through the hardening process as well. So that the separate file and separate things ran, so we've been talking a lot about that, I would say is probably the thing we've talked the most about in the last or 2 meetings. 

Speaker 1  (06:15)
Yeah, the only question I'm going to ask is, so it sounds like you. Are you know doing your ETL process? Which is great, and then the thing you didn't mention was analyzing at the end kind of once you got everything in your base form. 

Speaker 1  (06:31)
They're using plant. I'm using AI to help you with that. 

Speaker 2  (06:36)
I want to consider AI it's just different pricing rules. Define from, you know, retro sales, director of finance, of certain rules that we need to be in. It's basically an optimization problem. 

Speaker 2  (06:52)
I don't know if you know optimization problems within business analytics or analytics in general. 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
I'm not as fami. 

Speaker 2  (06:59)
So so you've basically define, so in terms the whole optimization problem is an analytical problem. So I guess by nature, it is an AI. But you define what metrics you want to maximize or minimize, and then create different rules to play Within bounds, right? 

Speaker 2  (07:19)
And so unless aspect, we're maximizing revenue by adjusting prices aparts within parameters rules, so I guess you can call it AI. 

Speaker 1  (07:34)
At what mechanism are you using to do that analyzation, are you using software? Are you using AI to help you with that? 

Speaker 2  (07:40)
AI is building the software. So I think So for example, adjust the prices of these ensuring that each of the price item or each of the individual items have a 30% margin. Another rule is within 25% of our competitors. 

Speaker 2  (08:00)
Another rule is don't make any pricing change more than 25%. If you consider AI, I Primarily wouldn't using, but it's an analytical problem. What's the tool are using to actually do that? 

Speaker 2  (08:19)
It perplexes, proplexity, but it's just I mean, you could do it in Excel using different time. 

Speaker 3  (08:25)
All right. 

Speaker 2  (08:26)
And in theory, under the definition of AI, a lot of stuff you build and Excel is considered AI. 

Speaker 3  (08:31)
All right. 

Speaker 1  (08:32)
I guess of course another would be so you talk about pieces and parts and costs for each piece and part. Are you like I I'm going to ask the question and you can tell me if I'm at a bounce because you're the data science and I am not so I will not pretend so are you having it look down to the part and be like, well, I know you said you had a 30% markup. But what if we could cost this part if we bought it from somebody else, that's even cheaper like, are you looking at it from those avenues to you? 

Speaker 2  (09:07)
Why not? But I do so? We've kind of ignored this from what I've heard. 

Speaker 2  (09:17)
For quite a few years. So we're behind a ball on this. I do have a broken out for identify parts where our cost exceeds our lowest competitor we have no opportunity to gain anything, because our cost so that will feed back to supply chain on opportunities to look at purchasing. 

Speaker 2  (09:40)
But Absolute. So I add a demo this morning, these type of things and desires are ones when you think of software development like, you should identify the requirements. The personas, the use cases and work through that We have a problem that we don't have I just try to say the right political way of we have a problem that we need to solve. 

Speaker 2  (10:08)
But we don't necessarily know how to solve it. And we don't know the right process to use to solve it. Then, let's try to work together to figure it out. 

Speaker 2  (10:15)
And put something in front of it to get some revenue gained and figure it out along the way. So I have a need and we'll feed into some of your work right as leading this is okay director of sales or I'm service that we need a resource to work back to build out the software program because right now, it's kind of been just what I know of not necessarily who the actual person is. That's going to use it. 

Speaker 2  (10:44)
Their processes of going through it, how they're going to identify it all that sort of stuff. So the people that used to do this are no longer here. We didn't backfill, so we lost that knowledge, and so we're trying to redo that. 

Speaker 1  (10:58)
No, no, that makes sense. 

Speaker 2  (11:01)
So there's probably opportunity there that would then have to dig into our purchasing supply chain data. That's one area of data that I had not gotten into. And honestly, this part stuff is kind of the first part of the part side. 

Speaker 3  (11:18)
And the other thing the supply chain is it gets kind of messy real quick because, you know, we have approved, you know, first and second tier vendors for some part cases. But some things don't have direct interchangeability, so there could be those plier that can make it for a cheaper price, but until we identify that supplier talk to them, find out quoting right, it's not so much that we have the accessible data to just plug and say, oh time to make the switch. From a to B it's more of a-okay, here's the information with which what to look for which is what I think you're 

Speaker 2  (11:49)
Yeah, and so you mean we go I think we have like 14000 acre repair parts. Well, in Seoul, like the approach that I'm taking here is only look at the top 500. It's a repair part's been in the top 500. 

Speaker 2  (12:07)
If any given year in the last 6 years, whether that's in quantity sold or the revenue gained search for those parts, which gets down to I think it was 300 in some parts, so you go from 14000 trying to figure out what to do to 300 from a competitive standpoint. And so then you can start putting price rules on that and make adjustments and the non-competitive ones. We have certain I guess pricing rules, but it's a way to kind of Focus down on a list. 

Speaker 2  (12:38)
You know, part of it. You know, maybe another follow question. You may have, well, one of the things we'll have to do is we'll have to go through our competitors and say, which ones are like-for-like parts, because we don't even know that we, you know. 

Speaker 2  (12:50)
So we have to go through 300 parts, not that bad of a list. But another Avenue, you can be like, well, I choose AI to determine whether they're similar, that would be great. If we had pictures of her own stuff, and then we can compare, or you can go based on descriptions, but then you're also making a large assumption that just their text is the same as our text. 

Speaker 2  (13:08)
So you can do it, I think it may just be easier to walk through 300 parts than trying to build out an AI model that tries to do that. If you can do picture competition, you can certainly run that through as well. And we don't have pictures of our parts. 

Speaker 3  (13:25)
Pictures of competitive parts either. 

Speaker 2  (13:28)
All the competitors on the website. 

Speaker 3  (13:29)
Well, you know, you just gotta scrape all the data individually, though. Still too, so I mean, the maintenance on that is still not free. 

Speaker 2  (13:37)
Anyways, that's one example. 

Speaker 1  (13:39)
You know, I think the only thing maybe is sounds like this is a ton of data. You're shifting through and like, you know, maybe an mcp in front of it or higher, the data is organized, whether it's database or flat files or you talked about. You haven't got into the product, was it? 

Speaker 1  (14:00)
The product there? The product sourcing, right? 

Speaker 2  (14:03)
It's like the piece of her kids. 

Speaker 1  (14:05)
Supply chain. Yeah, you know, putting some agents in front of those might help resolve some of the 

Speaker 3  (14:12)
We do have a sme in the department who held me at the next meeting. Actually, so if you have specific thoughts, questions around that 

Speaker 1  (14:19)
I think it's more. It sounds like where he's going. Obviously he's built some solid things going forward. 

Speaker 1  (14:26)
Obviously you're not a developer. You're not acknowledged that, but also like I don't know where you're at with a GitHub or anything, and she's like, but I think back to our discussion before I think that would help some of his concerns hope that he's expressed, which is like just helping standardize. Stuff that you're doing like give the AI like these are the standards we want you to meet and so not that you directly. 

Speaker 1  (14:50)
But telling your AI, these are the standards we want you to follow. And that 

Speaker 3  (14:55)
And just the development path, the development path, what is your point, where you're done and the handoff curve, and how does the handoff? 

Speaker 2  (15:03)
Head off to whoop. Exactly, yeah, so you're right. So I obviously have some IT background. 

Speaker 2  (15:09)
We have 12 years prior to coven here, so I understand GitHub repository as CIDC DCI Cid whatever. But if you go outside of you know me to other branches of this company. They don't feel they're not going to be knowledgeable of that. 

Speaker 2  (15:28)
And so I think we have to be a little careful of How what are expectations are of AI and who's actually using them to produce solutions? So we've been for if we're going from business to it, what handoffs and deliverables and expectations. 

Speaker 3  (15:50)
So nothing has decided yet, but what we are looking at is that there's likely to be a range of user skills that we would expect some of which will be approved to likely do higher level work, like what you're doing here in regards to these type of programs. So there's going to be different levels of programs, and then those will somehow match with the different skill sets, although how that gets structured in the process is still a lot to digest and do and then training of course to go up the scale as people want to improve those skills. 

Speaker 3  (16:23)
But it's not our intention is not for this, to be a Wild Wild West, free-for-all of anybody can just create anything and publish it into the system. Unvetted, unchecked, you know, their intention. Is there to be purposeful thoughts and checks and stages as part of that 

Speaker 2  (16:42)
That's why fear is, well, I just see, it's gonna be trying to prevent shadow it on steroid. 

Speaker 3  (16:47)
Yeah, that's gonna be 

Speaker 2  (16:49)
Do you want to talk about how many refreshable? Spreadsheets we have in this 

Speaker 3  (16:52)
Go for it. 

Speaker 2  (16:53)
I mean, because that's basically, you know, the fear of such happine. 

Speaker 3  (16:57)
Exploring, and you're exactly right. That mentality is very prevalent today. Refreshable, spreadsheets are 

Speaker 2  (17:05)
That word spreadsheets in general, well. 

Speaker 3  (17:06)
Threadsheets, in general and that's where the business continuity. You heard me says once in the it meeting? I've said it 15 times proper. 

Speaker 3  (17:13)
And that's where that's coming from is when we have somebody leaves that created Excel spreadsheet with a bunch of macros in it, because that's been that used to be the AI right to your point, that was the way people did the things and now they leave and nobody's maintaining that spreadsheet, and then like, where's that report or that data? And suddenly it's gone and nobody has access to the spreadsheet or they can't figure out how it works and are those things. So even when it comes to like these agent base systems What I've been talking to Doug about is so like we saw some wonderful things Zach's been working on. 

Speaker 3  (17:47)
And there are just standard agents, right? They're not coded based things, just agents in the system, but their knowledge repositories that are directly usable, searchable. And so what I would like to see is I have some thoughts on how we do a similar to the software side testing procedure, review, sign off procedure, and then I would like to see it transfer ownership from an individual to a service base account and the reason for that is the business continuity right then we have maintenance. 

Speaker 3  (18:14)
That falls under whoever that person is, maybe that's me, is the AI guy. Maybe that's it, maybe that's both. I don't know. 

Speaker 3  (18:21)
There's a lot of questions like that to me to be vetted, but the risk of the shadow piece is still extremely high, so finding the balance between process to make sure that we're getting clean solutions and not being so burdensome and cumbersome, that people don't want to do the process is gonna be main balancing act 

Speaker 1  (18:43)
I think yeah, and you know, the back to that I've lived some of those things where, like so-and-so did all that, and then they left and so it's like, and it's, you know, and the other thing is like they left it in such a state is like they're the only ones that can figure it out and so but you know, making the standard of hey, when you do something, AI related or agent related and is that all of a sudden we need you to put this into get hub and into some sort of document repository. So we have something as a company to fall back to whether you and the latter and you decide you're done or whatever that issue is, and you're no longer with a company, we still like, these are things we depend on like said, weren't that report, go, you know, and so having that stuff. 

Speaker 1  (19:30)
Documented and in a place where everybody can get to it. If need be, then it's there. So that would be the concern that I would, you know, to say yeah, there's a lot of things a lot of companies follow the under that same realm of like so-and-so did that, and now they're gone, and we don't know what they did to do that. 

Speaker 1  (19:49)
And so determ 

Speaker 3  (19:50)
Especially that's separate of AI. Yeah, that is, for example, a concern has existed. 

Speaker 1  (19:55)
But, you know, yeah, the, you know, the shadow, it is definitely, you know, the things that we've been kind of talking about is, like, how do we or how do you guys? You know, define that process of we're going to start here. And that's what I said is like you have to start someplace if you don't start, then you don't, you're not really doing anything. 

Speaker 1  (20:14)
So it's like you define this, but everybody knows it's a living and growing process here, because we don't know where the end is. But we're gonna start here and as we move through this process, we're going to learn things we can adjust as we move along to get there. And so the seam of what you're doing, and you're going to hand it off to somebody T eventually that right now that's undefined, you know, but, you know, maybe by the time you get there in 3 months, it's already defined, but yet this was handed to you and you messing with it now, right? 

Speaker 1  (20:49)
Because Brian created it, you'd yours now or together, however, it is right, and then all of a sudden, maybe fine. Well, this is the text act that IT knows, and you guys wrote it in in this, and so how do I get it from this to the text act that IT can support, and that's not on you. It's not on anybody else, but nothing was defined. 

Speaker 1  (21:13)
And so moving forward, it's like, let's define that text stack and yes is would python be better than go would rust be better than this would this front end be better than that depends, but you have to pick what people can support when you just can't let it be a free-for-all. Especially what a smaller company like Pearson needs to do the same thing as they would. I kind of like groups go off on their own and do their stuff, and they build something, and then that group kind of disbanded yet we had this thing. 

Speaker 1  (21:41)
And like Well, nobody knows that except for those individual peoples and they're all scattered out in different groups. Now. So it's like finding that support mechanism. 

Speaker 1  (21:51)
And so that's where defining things and I think you're gonna run into this is probably the first year or so when you have this starting this out is like, okay, let's adjust to the text stack that we can support as a company and go from there and build it out. 

Speaker 3  (22:05)
Yeah, with the with the AI council piece that's one topic. I think we're at to push really, really quickly. It's gonna be tech stack. 

Speaker 3  (22:13)
Both as we've talked about AI tools as well as what we want the AI tools to create into language, wise and other things, and then those are going to be the 2 1st immediate items to address. Yeah, everything else is hugely important. But those are going to be the 2 big 1. 

Speaker 1  (22:28)
Well, and even in the 

Speaker 2  (22:31)
Anywhere. 

Speaker 1  (22:33)
Yeah, and the budget will be in, as you grow as you grow into this. Once again it's like, you know, when you talk about you guys are asking, you know, rois, and it's like, well, you can't really define how you're going to do that for a little while, because you don't know everything that you don't know, and so to make that picture, it's going to develop over time. 

Speaker 3  (22:53)
No, I think you're right on that. Like my intention is to put together what we know today on an ROI structure on small-scale. Projects and see what gets missed in that. 

Speaker 3  (23:01)
And then Well, iterate, over time, because that's how I did that product rois, too because I did those, and it started out as a very basic thing, and now it's quite complicated in a good way. Right, it's providing value, but it's not as simple as it used to be right. 

Speaker 1  (23:17)
And it's also, in, you know, like you were saying too. It's like, you know, just the adjustment period of you learning how to do something Vs somebody else doing something, you know, there's a big difference there too. So like you'll be up and running faster than somebody who hasn't touched anything with code or understanding what cicd is, or what CIA is, what CDC D 

Speaker 2  (23:35)
That's a normal person. Want to just build it all together in one package, right? Rather than breaking it down. 

Speaker 1  (23:41)
Margaret larsan and that's the other key too, is like how is it modularized? What is the you know how tightly coupled is? The whole solution Vs being decoupled, and do we have this does this? 

Speaker 1  (23:54)
And this is its own reco, and this does this, and it's its own repo and you know, those type of things because it really should be their own reco or yet these 2 do need to have their own repo, but yet there still are separate because they are coupled together because they talk to each other and so you know that how all that plays out and that's something you guys have to figure out as you move along is like, okay, you've built this and that's where it was like, you know, first off of well, here's my business case, okay, we approve it now. 

Speaker 1  (24:23)
These are the rules you gotta follow by go build your proof of concepts and when they come and give you the proof of concept and show that it works. Then, it's like, okay, let's inspect on how you built it and did you follow some of the rules and that's where, like, okay, let's make sure, you know, one of the rules in which I didn't mention before is like, let's make sure that we're not. Take the couple together when we don't need to be, you know, and so make ensuring that that rule is followed. 

Speaker 1  (24:47)
When you tell AI to build something out for you, there's nothing wrong with having A. Here's my paragraph prompt go. Do it as long as you have guidelines for the AI to follow that beats the standard. 

Speaker 1  (24:58)
You want to have it. So 

Speaker 2  (25:03)
I think Be able to be a little bit more accelerated in this being a little bit more agile and building out teams of trying to solve specific The challenges that I think 

Speaker 1  (25:18)
Oh, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (25:20)
Can you go? 

Speaker 3  (25:21)
Yeah, the other thing is, you know, most conversations we've had today, I would say, have been centered more around these larger scale tools, right things that would likely become enterprise releases, and I think there's a lot of opportunity probably in the middle ground. And I think it was processes will probably end up being different. This is somebody who needs this, like Zack was running a script. 

Speaker 3  (25:42)
He had created a script for come cross, referencing data to date. I think you helped hold data for the subsidies, right? Yeah, so he's using that script to cross-reference that day with some other data. 

Speaker 3  (25:54)
And say, oh, this is a really not a really. I think there's a ton of those middle ground opportunities like that, which are really specific to individuals' workflows, the question is how much do we need to regulate those if at all, and how do we manage those? Because when Zac leaves that still, you know, just within his local sphere. 

Speaker 3  (26:14)
So I think there's some questions on. Maybe there is a way to have these individuals have some more free form control, but maybe we need to just like catalog them, right to your point, get hybrid pository. Something searchable database for people can go into. 

Speaker 3  (26:27)
I'm looking for a tool to do rois. Oh, here's an ROI tool somebody made, but then the question is, how is it vetted? It's eveted, is not vetted? 

Speaker 3  (26:35)
More questions? The answer than our answer. But 

Speaker 1  (26:38)
Once again, I still think defining a text tax tax 

Speaker 3  (26:42)
Oh, yeah, it's gotta happen in the front end. 

Speaker 1  (26:43)
As you can't Any language can do anything. And sometimes my language is better than the other language to do it. But if you have the text act defined, and like, he's the first one I've ever seen in the company mention python, and so I'm not, I don't have anything against python, I do it myself, but also, like if you don't hand anybody else who can not that he's reading the code or supporting it. 

Speaker 1  (27:06)
But if you had somebody in the company that could, then it's a little easier Vs being like, hey, you know, write it in this Vs python, even though it might not be the best language, but it will still get the job done. It's like what are you? It's a you're not writing in this particular case, you weren't writing a browser. 

Speaker 1  (27:27)
You were writing a batch down a back end. So if it takes A minute longer? Is it really that much of a kill? 

Speaker 1  (27:34)
You know, versus, because you wrote it in one language that wasn't quite as efficient Vs like, you know, if I'm, I need to process 900000 files and I need to process it now, even if it's a batch job, I want that to be as fishing as possible Vs like, that's a good job isn't quite that pressing. And so therefore that's where you gotta kind of really justify one language or whatever it is. 

Speaker 2  (27:57)
I think we're a little bit In today's Environment, we're using AI and spits out primarily crossbord, it spits out a python, and I don't think there's anybody to interpret it. I would Say I can interpret it. I'm not I don't use it daily to be able to be proficient in it. 

Speaker 2  (28:28)
But obviously going through schooling. I used it right, so I can't at least read it and understand it. I don't think a lot of others in any environment can, and I think that's a risk 

Speaker 3  (28:42)
For sure, the question 

Speaker 2  (28:44)
I mean, everything's good. 

Speaker 1  (28:45)
Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 3  (28:46)
Yeah, the question is, what level of vetting process needs to happen? And then what level of risk are we willing to accept? 

Speaker 2  (28:53)
And so that's been a little bit of a challenge, though, I'm 3 years here now. The challenge that I continue to face is getting deep inside something, whether it's python, and building up pythons, and doing it maybe efficient. And maybe the right way at risk of nobody else being able to understand that if I leave kids, he's scrutiny or do more dragon drop software of workflows, where people can understand it better and be able to support it, that's like the dilemma that I face daily on that. 

Speaker 2  (29:31)
So jumping into data standpoint I use a powerbi to do the majority of my visualization in dashboards. It's been on my list of putting together a fabric. Lake counts. 

Speaker 2  (29:48)
So that continues, get pushed off, so we don't have really an enterprise warehouse, correct? We have an ERP system that is, for the most part built Around our processes, with connected and sometimes disconnected processes and systems, but that's something I think is a wrist store company of and a need to put together better tightly processes to support our data and understand how our process affect the quality of our data. I see that as an underlying risk to the AI deployment of 

Speaker 1  (30:28)
Yeah 

Speaker 3  (30:29)
Clemland is of our data is a concern to me as well, especially when we look at the history of how our data was created in some specific areas. More than others engineering is the classic example, because we obviously used to have hand-drawn stuff, and then we went to AutoCAD and we went to a monocad to inventor and then went to inventor to solidworks. And some a lot of that has been remodeled in terms of what's active, but depending on how it was remodeled, when it was remodeled, how clean that data is in terms of the CAD documentations, the CAD data itself, I should say, and in some cases the documentation. 

Speaker 3  (31:03)
So yes, data cleanliness is a significant concern to me. Obviously the data management where it ISIS a concern also, but that's I don't have as much exposure to that side as the we'll say. I want to say later. 

Speaker 2  (31:17)
I think data ownership is also a huge concern. 

Speaker 1  (31:21)
What do you guys use in for our pipeline? 

Speaker 2  (31:30)
Myself, parvia. Depending on the dashboard report that's built. But primarily the power query aspect of power Pi we don't have A Fabric license? 

Speaker 2  (31:49)
That's on the 2 list. I do build out python scripts on some of them to extract external. Sources. 

Speaker 2  (32:00)
There are also custom store procedures and scripts that run in various environments from an IQ standpoint to move data to different systems or to Do stuff, I guess yeah, that's prior to my 

Speaker 1  (32:16)
No, yeah, I mean, sometimes you just inherit stuff, and that's why it goes 

Speaker 2  (32:21)
But on that topic, like Part of me has looked into airflow or other Pythonish style of open source technology. But again, the dilemma is if we go down that path, it's gonna be very hard for somebody else to help support it. So in my mind where I was going was since we're already a Microsoft shop. 

Speaker 2  (32:50)
I'm already using, 0 3 65. Continue down the path of power BI in fabric in the use of that. I would have I'm much rather used to have low but we don't have salesforce so financially. 

Speaker 2  (33:05)
It doesn't make sense with the cost of tableau. Um, that's kind of where I'm My thinking goes I don't mean how much about fabric or power B? I'm gonna speak 

Speaker 1  (33:21)
Just a little bit like, I'm not AI understand the concepts of data science and data engineering. But not the software I've learned, you know, as you're much, don't get into it. So I mean, that's huh. 

Speaker 1  (33:33)
Yeah, AWS, yeah, so it's kind 

Speaker 2  (33:36)
A combination of she was a the best ones. That's a redshift for is that their day wearing out soon or right redshift, and glue, and There are visualizations like insights. Yeah, I think so. 

Speaker 2  (33:53)
Azure is a combination of Snowflake. Power BI is a visualization and Your E Tl is data bricks, I think 

Speaker 1  (34:11)
Yeah, um, yeah. So it sounds like basically, there's a disconnect with the data pipeline and how people just as a company. Overall moving data around, there's a lot of Add hoc things at work. 

Speaker 1  (34:31)
You have to be in the know in order to know which button to push when to push it. You probably have some documentation on it. But there's no overall giant pitcher of this is from point a to point Z is how we get there other than, like, maybe some documentation or maybe some jobs that might Otto kick off, might not auto kick off is that kind of the true 

Speaker 2  (34:55)
I would summarize it that over time. All of our systems have different scripts that push stated away they need to go I don't think we have a good data governance system in maintaining the process, the support the data structure or no enterprise warehouse. 

Speaker 1  (35:18)
And then you get or you were. So you're in the cloud in a zur, or are you in the cloud? 

Speaker 2  (35:26)
The only. Department, that. In my opinion is using cloud. 

Speaker 2  (35:33)
For maybe 10 purposes, is the North Liberty office. We have 365 to support, you know, share point teams all that stuff outside of that, we're not really easy to adjure. 

Speaker 3  (35:47)
Yeah, I think ITV use 

Speaker 2  (35:49)
So in northern Gray is using AWS, yeah Okay, so that's kind of another I don't know. I throw out. It's a risk to our company. 

Speaker 2  (35:58)
When you see For the most part, things moving to the cloud when it makes sense. Sometimes you get more expensive moving the cloud, depending on what you have. But Skill wise. 

Speaker 2  (36:12)
That is another risk. Because a lot of people tie AI hide and cloud together I keep getting Surface base structure and the only people that have really been the same. The knowledge right now of the cloud is North Liberty, our it team does, from an Azure standpoint. 

Speaker 2  (36:30)
Through 75, they wouldn't even think of different services that are bill or how to utilize cloud for different capabilities own North Liberty really has. The 

Speaker 3  (36:41)
And we'll get to meet the thunder Wednesday. 

Speaker 1  (36:43)
Yeah, Joe, yeah, no I think, yeah, I think the concerns you've expressed that would probably have the same ones. Basically, as like lack of some sort of workflow. Some tool to help you manage everything. 

Speaker 1  (36:58)
And it sounds like it's not even just in your area. It sounds like it's even just more broader than that. And so kind of getting everybody on the same page, this goes down to, like, all right, how do we? 

Speaker 1  (37:08)
How do we keep the robot from running through the data centers? The information isn't secure enough. You can't say I have. 

Speaker 1  (37:16)
I am my policies on all of our data. And they can't touch it right, because right now you have a scattered system. 

Speaker 3  (37:25)
Yeah, we have data silos. I don't know that that means that they're unsecure. 

Speaker 1  (37:28)
Well, but you're saying it's like, in order to really give yourself a better picture and I'm not trying to no no push to the cloud. Or not push to the cloud, but having an overall picture of how things work together, you're going to be more efficient overall. 

Speaker 3  (37:41)
For sure, IA 100% agree and warehousing has been a topic we've discussed since I don't know at least last 6 years. Probably when we first started the European victory. But for sure, in the last 3 years, because we were looking at some ERP stuff and there was a tension to do exactly that. 

Speaker 3  (37:57)
So I don't even I'm not anti warehouse at all. But I am just saying that silo doesn't necessarily mean I'm secure, but 

Speaker 1  (38:03)
So you see, I'm saying, like, if we kind of if we give AI the keys to do something. And is it, are we sure that all of our information is inside the data center and not accessible by the bot? And if it either kind of scattered, that's a lot of check boxes, the check and make sure that everything is the way it's supposed to be. 

Speaker 3  (38:26)
As a concern, no I agree. 

Speaker 1  (38:28)
So but yeah. 

Speaker 2  (38:30)
I mean, the first year and a 1 the reason why I don't have a parenthouse, which largely probably falls on my responsibility. The first year and a 1 we were going through ERP that got canceled. Then he ag, turned 

Speaker 3  (38:44)
To c***. 

Speaker 2  (38:46)
And then budgets were tightened, and so that's why we I haven't really pursued it. In another priorities, getting in the way on 

Speaker 1  (38:53)
No, I'm not forgive 

Speaker 2  (38:56)
President Treasury, I'm just that, I think That's I mean. Depending on what we're going after I mean, you can't have a good AI solution without good quality data in the process of support data. So if we don't have that we're jumping from 0 to a 100 without a vehicle. 

Speaker 1  (39:20)
Look, yeah. 

Speaker 3  (39:21)
The other question for that, though, is, you know, the warehouses, one piece of it, but that's storage, not data itself. 

Speaker 1  (39:26)
A little pipeline. Does the overall process 

Speaker 2  (39:29)
I know we're at Lake House. Yeah, is what I would suggest. 

Speaker 1  (39:34)
Just that overall pipeline, that the overall access of we know this is the process, because, you know, I think part of what he's iterating here is that if he were to leave, then a lot of knowledge lost in that aspect Vs like if you had Per se and I'm just gonna a workflow tool that is, I push a button, and it goes dude. I can see the progress go if we've done all you've done all your stuff. You've written all the code you've written all the patches, the scripts and everything, and it all works seamlessly, then somebody can go in. 

Speaker 1  (40:10)
And actually, look at what's going on and document 

Speaker 3  (40:13)
My point is this pipeline's great. It's useless if the oil's bad. 

Speaker 1  (40:17)
Right? Right? And that's but that's part of 

Speaker 2  (40:19)
The pipeline should be turning your oil gasoline. 

Speaker 3  (40:22)
Right? Fancy pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (40:25)
But I mean, you have to build out again each of the pile play. So they want to call it utl or elt, right? You create the raw data, and then you injust it into better quality data along the way, which you have one of the challenges is that I don't know the manufacturing. 

Speaker 2  (40:41)
I don't know the engineering. I don't know the supply chain. I don't know the financial service, so I almost have to have somebody sit with me through defining these pipelines against who doesn't have availability. 

Speaker 2  (40:52)
All those people, right? 

Speaker 1  (40:54)
Whereas, like even he's got all these sources and to bring all those sources together through the ETL process to make the data, look the same, for lack of a better term, I'm not trying to simplify it, but to get it to a usable point for the rest of the company. 

Speaker 3  (41:08)
Yeah, so that's my whole point. Though is that our data? I don't know if it's even clean enough for that simplistic conversion. 

Speaker 3  (41:16)
The evidence. That's my point is that we talk about the pipeline we're talking about. The connection point I think, more fundamentally, the question is, is our data ready to convert. 

Speaker 3  (41:26)
And I don't know that answer 

Speaker 2  (41:28)
That's why I think it can be. I think some of the risks to that is, do we have Consistent processes for when we enter things. So for example, I think your data silo point is very valid. 

Speaker 2  (41:46)
One area or department could make a decision on how to enter data that makes it the easiest for them. It creates a whole big of a mask downstream, so give you one example all right. Order codes we go from one model. 

Speaker 2  (42:04)
Let's take a 36 

Speaker 3  (42:08)
We have like 15 bases, 12 

Speaker 2  (42:10)
Bro 30 inch model. We give it a one order code this year and a new one last the year before we get a new one this year. So like it may be easier, maybe from an engineer and I don't know, but it makes it a hell a lot harder to 

Speaker 3  (42:24)
Enjoy all the data. It actually has a home to do downstream and with customers, and build a material structure in this specific example. So if there's not in theory, if it's not backwards compatible, it needs to be a new number. 

Speaker 3  (42:36)
So when you're not looking forward, let's say you're looking forward only one year instead of 3 years, then it doesn't really matter actually. Based off your resourcing, your constrained on when you're going to do projects, but let's say you're gonna make a change that changes the entire weldman on the wing. For example, now that weld mint, that's in your bill material for that order. 

Speaker 3  (42:54)
Code is no longer convictable, a better example. 

Speaker 2  (42:59)
Bixby yeah, beast, cool, little model changes has been changing quite a bit last Thursday, so when you think of it from A A dealer trying to order it or find inventory on it now. For example, at 36 0 5. They want to find a 12030 inch machine. 

Speaker 2  (43:17)
They gotta pick four different word codes to find. That model within our inventory and they have to know that 

Speaker 3  (43:26)
But from it, okay? So from an engineering perspective, though piece 

Speaker 2  (43:30)
It was talking about it from a dealer perspective. 

Speaker 3  (43:32)
Sure, but what I'm saying is that as an engineering perspective. If you leave the code the same, then it implies that every single year that that code is the same has the same structure underneath it. Which is a problem right? 

Speaker 3  (43:43)
If you need to go back inwards in time and look at something you're right. The dealer facing, that's kind of a problem. But it's only kind of a problem based off of inventory that has been unsold correct, and that context. 

Speaker 3  (43:54)
Because when you go into the portal to order a new code, you only have the option for that code that's active for that model year, except for when you get to attachments, then attachments is where things get really messy, at least my opinion attachment side, that's where messy 

Speaker 2  (44:09)
So I get like this example to get mexic, it makes sense for engineering. 

Speaker 3  (44:15)
And yeah, it's agreed from all 

Speaker 2  (44:17)
For areas that when you step back, you're 

Speaker 3  (44:19)
And I would actually know so far to say is that not only makes sense for the engineering side, it is a requirement from the structure of engineering to do their job effectively, both forward and backwards patable, that doesn't mean there's not another way to do it effectively, but it is a requirement to have some differentiation year-over-year, when you make big product changes, that is a requirement. How that happens separate different conversation? So, until somebody comes up with a better way that also serves the other things downstreams. 

Speaker 3  (44:47)
Fortunately, that's where we have for data Phip. 

Speaker 1  (44:49)
So basically, there's a not a lack of but a difficult process this morning. The ETL process is very difficult. 

Speaker 2  (45:01)
Or the thing that really Yeah, okay, even if we go, don't worry. 

Speaker 1  (45:05)
Yeah, you're good. 

Speaker 3  (45:06)
I'm not taking needle fish lists. 

Speaker 2  (45:09)
We don't have a mechanism that says. Again, if you want to track all I realize the fundamental of changing the components better, right? When you think of it as a 360512 row 30 inch. 

Speaker 2  (45:21)
I don't care about everything else from you. That's like what customers look for right and we don't. We need to create a we don't have it today. 

Speaker 2  (45:30)
We need to create it a way to track the evolution of a 360512 row 30. 

Speaker 3  (45:38)
Yeah, because right now, other 

Speaker 2  (45:39)
Under, you know, order codes throughout the years, the fundamentally, this is a model ro. 

Speaker 3  (45:45)
Amazing, and that's exactly you actually pointed yourself back to the reason why engineering does it to some degree? Because in conceptually, if it's a small change, then they wouldn't change the order code itself, right? Something that's compatible for an backwards. 

Speaker 3  (46:00)
Let's say we changed apart. There's new holes in play. Okay, well, that extra hole in play doesn't matter to the customer, so they're buying it. 

Speaker 3  (46:06)
For the new thing, the order code can stay the same. 

Speaker 2  (46:09)
I'm driving even further for you. Let's hear alright, so SLT comes to me and says, hey, we want to forecast a prediction of what our sales are going to be this year. 

Speaker 3  (46:18)
Oh, yeah, this one is a good one. 

Speaker 2  (46:19)
I don't ask because I don't know. Sort of so fine. I can't track the salesworth. 

Speaker 3  (46:24)
No, this is a good example that's a great 

Speaker 2  (46:25)
I mean, I had to create my own solution for but that was a real world problem, my old, I can't like, I don't know. I don't know if because we don't have good quality data to track over the years of this went from hugging 4900 to 49 11 5 to 15 900. 

Speaker 3  (46:42)
Third, and that's what a lot of the changes can 

Speaker 1  (46:46)
Oh, so if If you gave AI access, do you think it could figure that out? 

Speaker 2  (46:57)
Uh, I would think so. Based on item descriptions and item code 

Speaker 3  (47:02)
Like the we have these 

Speaker 1  (47:03)
Well, they could. 

Speaker 2  (47:04)
I mean, I basically 

Speaker 1  (47:05)
You're doing the work, but it's right. But it may not be translating it right? But if we are able to give AI access to the data store that you needed and gave it to be like all right, this is what we need to do and create your cross lookup table. 

Speaker 1  (47:20)
Then, you would be able then to help create processes that would uh U. Populate that cross-reference table and then you can create other scripts or Webpage, whatever, then that could give you the information as needed. 

Speaker 2  (47:38)
I mean, I basically created 

Speaker 1  (47:41)
I know you created 8 years 

Speaker 2  (47:42)
You know, I basically looked at model row number spacing, size and created a mapping, so I'm sure I could come up with a much better way. 

Speaker 1  (47:51)
Right. But like, you know, I think that the time spent you did that then. But then, having AI kind of help you get over that home and then also like expand it to make it useful for not only you but anybody else that needs. 

Speaker 1  (48:04)
So they wouldn't always have to come to you. Be like, go check the webpage. 

Speaker 2  (48:08)
And I have an I say, no, my list, the last thing is to create nothing to do. 

Speaker 1  (48:13)
But I mean, that sounds like a solid project. Though I'm not saying it's easy, I'm you know, but I'm just saying it's like, that's definitely a solid project to be the hey, that's but 

Speaker 3  (48:22)
It would 

Speaker 2  (48:24)
It would be a sort of a one time thing, and then you work it within your process of engineering. Anytime you go from one order code to another. Add this entry into the data vis. 

Speaker 1  (48:33)
Bright, that's what I'm saying is, like, you know, you can create, yes, it's a one time AI project you're not, but you're building a set of code that does the work, adding your database procedures, or whatever it is you wanted to have done. 

Speaker 3  (48:46)
I think though, this also brings up another interesting point, when we talk about projects, project approvals, which we haven't talked about yet, which is great project, which is better for the company doing this project or changing a process 

Speaker 1  (48:59)
And those are valid points. And that's where you can also use AI be. Like, all right, what's what's if we do this, we create this cross-reference lookup table, what are we looking at for hours? 

Speaker 1  (49:09)
Versus if we have to change the process, what does that look like, and then you can do a solid comparison to that point, versus everybody trying to understand you could create a good little summary of doing this Vs doing that, and what the word does that get you? Yeah? 

Speaker 3  (49:24)
Yeah, cause like in this context. Contextual example like, we talk about the order code changing as the foundational piece. But maybe the order code base order code isn't the thing we should be referencing? 

Speaker 3  (49:34)
Maybe there should be a secondary attribute that it never changes right for 3012 or 36 0 5. It is always I'm gonna throw a random thing. But this attribute AB QA BQ for that, all right. 

Speaker 3  (49:46)
So every time you go and you're like, oh, last year ABQI sold this many, even though the number changed functionally, the model you're right largely not different. So I mean, there's other ways to handle that. That's a what appears to be a relatively easy process change Vs creating a custom script of the tool. 

Speaker 3  (50:04)
Now, there's education. There's training. There's new things that come along 

Speaker 1  (50:08)
But also you could have your plane and be like all right, this is kind of my plan of what I want. Have AI come up 2 or 3 of them. See what it comes up with 2, you know, and that once again is like, you know, given it that access to the silo or scrub it and enough to where it's like, okay, this is what I need you to look at. 

Speaker 3  (50:25)
The other question too, though, is how much I mean the worst part about that is right now, I don't know how we would give access to AI to understand current process flows, which I think would help it, but generate better alternatives. So that's another second something else to consider. Is there a way to input process flows? 

Speaker 3  (50:42)
Whenever we talk about 

Speaker 1  (50:44)
So there is, and that is the 5 can do it. I think the app is a little bit better. I think cloud code but talk through it. 

Speaker 1  (50:56)
You sit down and you have a conversation, it's like we're doing right now and then we can be like, all right, go ahead, take the translation and give me that overflow of what's going on. Right, but you know what I'm saying is like, everybody can talk about it. You can put it all together into and have the AI. 

Speaker 1  (51:16)
Analyze the information and say, okay, what is this workflow? Look like? Now what pieces are we missing? 

Speaker 1  (51:22)
And then everybody can kind of review it and identify the gas and be like almost crack fit. More like this. And then you can improve that process to get to where you want to be. 

Speaker 1  (51:31)
And then you can take that and then identify any other gaps, you're like, we got a gap here or take this suction, and we circle it. And be like, okay. These 3 processes, how can we improve that? 

Speaker 1  (51:43)
What does that look like? I think that's a good way to do it and have AI, like I said, you talk about every now you don't have it, you can get there, have a ID the translation by somebody just talking through it and help you get there and make your adjustments from that. 

Speaker 3  (51:59)
Very interesting interesting thought. So ok, technically, we have like 7 minutes left. I'd like to cover this off while early sea. 

Speaker 3  (52:07)
I have a chance to take a break before you get into the large group. So I'd say, if you have any final questions for this meeting, we can wrap up hey, Susie. 

Speaker 2  (52:16)
So are your brains exploding at 

Speaker 3  (52:20)
So far, they're intact, but we still got 2 more hours. 

Speaker 1  (52:24)
All 

Speaker 2  (52:25)
I didn't know if he needed a couple extra minutes to get set up in the hour. 

Speaker 3  (52:29)
We're going to finish up now and head that way to 

Speaker 2  (52:31)
And then I gotta step out 345, I'm gonna be over there in the back. But don't be alarmed or offended. If I step out, because I gotta take care of someone 345, and then I'll be back with you at 4, you and Gary to kind of just wrap up the day. 

Speaker 2  (52:44)
So yeah, okay, we'll see you in a minute. All right, thank you I mean, there's all our opportunities to use AI that I haven't talked about. 

Speaker 3  (52:55)
The more forecasting production stuff you've had a meeting together for you and me to kind of go over some of that tomorrow. I think Korea I think you're on that list 
