
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Here you go, all right. So basically I'm gonna kind of let you describe the things you want to talk about. Because I don't know anything that you're doing. 

Speaker 1  (00:10)
I will try to provide insight where I can 

Speaker 2  (00:13)
Okay, Ola, I kind of just give him a rundown Garrett like I did you the other day so I'm gonna go ahead and connect to The TV give you a better view. 

Speaker 2  (00:34)
All right, I'll probably have it mirrored. I wonder that should be good enough. I'll just do like a dual screen. 

Speaker 2  (00:56)
There we go. Well, I guess lately, the most recent project I've been using ChatGPT for is T-shirt design, so I'll just kind of show you some of the designs real quick, but really not using it for imaging as much as you'd think I do a lot of the production here, photography 3D. As well as the digital advertising with Meta at Google and then, you know, just the longer list of everything else. 

Speaker 2  (01:25)
So small team at the moment. So we're kind of stepping up to just, you know, feels a lot of voids and ais doing a great job doing that. But yeah, so just so that she shared designs, this is actually a photo I did. 

Speaker 2  (01:37)
But these ChatGPT to help us do something that would be viable for t-shirts. We won't probably go into much imaging after that, but I figured since that's been kind of some recent stuff that's Some of the current work. But let's start from the top. 

Speaker 2  (01:54)
So one of the big things that I really utilize ChatGPT with is these custom GPT agents and it's not completely Agentic AI. But it's also, you know, different ways. I use ChatGPT through different steps. 

Speaker 2  (02:11)
So, for instance, there's this one called Kinsey insights, and now Kinsey insights is a all-knowing Kinsey product. But it was really created. When we needed to replace a copywriter, our copywriter left the company so kinsian sites is really programmed to be a really elaborate and well communicated, also to mimic brand voice and whatnot. 

Speaker 2  (02:41)
Man, then one of the few things that it kind of makes it more custom. It has all the operators manuals plus our updated literature. It does have web access, but it's really guided to make sure it stays within the updated literature and operators and also reference what it's talking about. 

Speaker 2  (02:58)
This has helped automate social media. A lot of our web copy and stuff like that. Now there's a dumb down version on copilot, and we're going to be allowing some of our new sales managers to access that. 

Speaker 2  (03:12)
So they can answer questions faster, since they're new to the company. And they're not going to have all the product knowledge in their brain yet. So Kinsey insights has been a great 1I think Gary, that's when I've shared with you the first one I made, and I'm gonna just turn on. 

Speaker 2  (03:31)
Do Not Disturb for the time being. So we don't get Messages. Does actually BT though my name is Zach zach, by the way, so Zach GPT is my AI assistant, your + 1 yeah and so Zack GPT does. 

Speaker 2  (03:47)
Is he's? It's understands how to utilize AI tools for projects. So a lot of times this is my starting point even to write prompts for me. 

Speaker 2  (03:57)
So I prompt, the prompts is what I like to say. So it can help me, you know, get a little bit more recommendations and troubleshooting and thoughts. And I'll just kind of go down a quick list of my other ones, and we'll go too deep on each you can kind of see how I'm building them out. 

Speaker 2  (04:15)
Kinsey, welb, troubleshooter understands everything we do with our website. Our website's completely done on house on blue hosts and WordPress CSS, custom CSS is involved in whatever type of coding language that we need that day, it helps with. We have a marketing strategist helps with campaigns and whatsnot hub spot operations advisor this is a new one because colleague mine's retiring. 

Speaker 2  (04:38)
And he's our hub, spot guy, we're backfilling, but for the time being, you know, hubspot specialists will be nice to be able to ask questions too. I'm in hubspot daily as well and set up workflows when needed. But Scott really leads that part of things. 

Speaker 2  (04:53)
So this will just help with some of that as well. VR specialist, self-explanatory event planner came about when we were doing a certain setup for this innovation day gave us a starting point kind of outlined the day, and now we've just been customizing that ag market analyst, planner, competitive and market intelligence dealer due diligence. When we get a new dealer, it can really dive in deep. 

Speaker 2  (05:18)
And I usually use the deep research side of things to dig at a new dealer application to see if there's anything from the Better Business Bureau, or any bankruptcies or any arrest records like it does vendor due diligence has been nice too for when we're looking at third party vendors and with one example recent was that market pilot, which you've probably already been filled in that we're kind of putting together a parts price comparison software. And so market pilot was the vendor we were looking at with this agent was able to do was give us a really nice text stack of how market pilot did what it did. 

Speaker 2  (05:53)
It's a little bit of python, a little bit of AI, a little bit of webscaping. So operator support assistants. I don't really use these much, but we are trying to get them a little more perfected, and it's been a work in progress with References, the operator's manual of a certain model and a very, really great at the operator's manual and then also we want to branch into parts. 

Speaker 2  (06:15)
So on service needs to look up a part. I can get a number like that. And video production assistant, which in my custom gpts, is named Quinton gptino. 

Speaker 2  (06:24)
But yeah, I do all the video work here in documentary work. So it's helped me just kind of you know, title screen stuff like that, but also my workflow, when it comes to production, it's Titan things up and whatnot there's business impact ChatGPT. Help me kind of put all of my nominee, so the next one I think you're going to get more of a kick out of because you're in the data world. 

Speaker 2  (06:49)
I kind of looked up on LinkedIn, python stuff like that. So this one is lead vetting data. Intelligence so we have hubspot for our CRM. 

Speaker 2  (06:58)
No question, we always get, are they farmers, even though we're doing targeting and custom lists, we're still going to get people that aren't farmers to sign up for high productivity, plant or guide, like those lead magnets. Generally, that's the top of our funnel. There's a lot more steps until they get to a salesman or a dealership, but lead magnets to the top of the funnel. 

Speaker 2  (07:19)
So we've been using this python script that I kind of like Google collab has just made it really easy for me to put the change the script within ChatGPT. But what this is going to do this is our ewg matching is that I have 3 Excel sheets with about Oh, I don't know. Probably 80 + 1000 rows of Subsidy EWG data. 

Speaker 2  (07:47)
What that tells me if somebody has subsidies in the millions, they're probably farming, a lot of acres that just gives us an idea of acres. So what this does is our leads come in and we can match the script will match our hubspot CRM, which is an Excel sheet export when I bring it into this and then matches it with the Excel sheet that has its sub city data. The thought is to automate this completely with Agentic AI. 

Speaker 2  (08:13)
So then a leap comes into hub spot runs through the script script, finds, if it's that person that farmer has subsidies or ever financed a planner with ucc data, the ucc data one's great because it gives us What type of plan are there: if it's new reused finance? Or what kind of brand too? So I did these a year ago when we brushed them off recently for our next event, but I've been able to tighten up quite a bit, and it really gives us a good idea of if it says it's a match. 

Speaker 2  (08:47)
Now, it's really highly highly likely it's a match. But it also gives us ones to review meaning like the address matches. But the first name's different or something. 

Speaker 2  (08:57)
This uses fuzzy matching as well. So it understands to take liberties. If there's a Dan or a Daniel stuff like that. 

Speaker 2  (09:03)
So digital marketing content creation so some of those custom gpts really help figure out, you know, not only geography, we generally have a good idea what planners make sense where but it does give us a good help on starting points when it comes to Types of ads that are tactics that will work in different segments better. So like if it's like, let's do a younger demographic, it might say we'll try some of the Instagram reels the short content, right? We see a lot of our leads coming in through carousels on Meta meta is really a bread-and-butter of us for generating new leads at the top of that funnel. 

Speaker 2  (09:46)
So Uh, web development. I kind of introduced you to that web troubleshooter having the website internally. Well, it's really kind of just Sherri in myself that I are managing the website. 

Speaker 2  (10:00)
The Web troubleshooter comes in extremely handy. Recently, had hosting issues. We just We did not too long ago. 

Speaker 2  (10:08)
We switched from a shared server to dedicated, and the transition. AI helped quite a bit with helped negotiation as well. But Blue host did a pretty seamless transition. 

Speaker 2  (10:23)
For us, but there was a few things. We still had to use about troubleshooter for right? So recently that dedicated server went down, I was troubleshooting it. 

Speaker 2  (10:30)
I was looking into it and seeing if it was anything we could help, but it ended up being blue host had an attack. There was a cyber attack, which another we can do, and that's where that goes. And so, the website is back and run on in a couple hours. 

Speaker 2  (10:43)
But yep, that day I was calling customer service a lot. Yeah, social media just helping automate copy Kinsey insights. I mean, it listed out and outlined about 3 months of social media posts and that included copy call outs. 

Speaker 2  (11:04)
And then some of the imaging I do I do in Adobe express, because it's template, best based, and we used to have a couple graphic designers since they've left the company, another thing that we're just trying to use the resources as best we can, that we have. Then, custom, coding on another side of this, this is a couple different coding languages, not python, but this started in solid works from engineering. We brought that file into cinema 40. 

Speaker 2  (11:31)
That's what I do a lot of our 3D animation with how to export it to a glb. Because I was starting to the starting point for this animation, this interactive row unit really became and Google's model develop, that gave me the base code brought it into ChatGPT and figured out how to customize it, give us the hotspots. We liked and now you can kind of interact with this row unit and figure out the main features. 

Speaker 2  (12:01)
But I did have it put together a tech stack of every step we took. So it's HTML 5 with some CSS and Javascript embedded on the word press. And yeah, so it didn't take all that long to do this, it would have took longer if I didn't already have. 

Speaker 2  (12:19)
That's that model already finished. So I got it from solidworks. When the 5000 series launched, which would have been Probably 45 years ago, and so that road unit's been texturized, colorized and all that, you know, even just everything down to the Chrome on the bolts that was done years ago. 

Speaker 2  (12:39)
And now so that's what really sped this process up, because the manual stuff was all done, and it just really needed to be coded, so it could be embedded. So in a nutshell, that's what I'm using ChatGPT with, but every day is different with it. And yeah, there's not we have plenty of work to utilize it with and to fill in voids where we need like an expert and stuff. 

Speaker 1  (13:06)
So solid? 

Speaker 2  (13:08)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's been A. It's been a game changer for me. Definitely. 

Speaker 2  (13:15)
That even just like our hydraulic door specialist, you know, so somehow that we're in the hydraulic door space, I didn't know anything about hydraulic doors before a year ago. And so, this has been a huge help. It's wrote scripps, voiceover scripts, where I've brought that script into an AI voiceover and yeah, it's just helped with certain things like that. 

Speaker 1  (13:35)
Now, I think the only thing that I Is are you storing? Information in the Inn GitHub, it's not like so like this. Isn't your only master control like you have backup so someplace else? 

Speaker 2  (13:50)
No, I don't have these guys. I don't have any of Does it have any in my ChatGPT backed up anywhere? So that was that something would be a recommendation. 

Speaker 2  (13:58)
I would 

Speaker 1  (14:00)
Just from a standpoint of like and it, you know, not necessarily a nightly thing, but probably a weekly thing you just never know when things crash or go. 

Speaker 2  (14:08)
Yeah, and we back just like the website, I automate that back up. But I've never even thought of backing up ChatGPT I guess 

Speaker 1  (14:17)
Amazingly, we have some models built, and so that information those models is a stored someplace right there. And so I would definitely provide like, talk to it and be like, okay, how do I back up these? You know, models that I have built and have it, do a nightly Pole or a weekly poll to where it pulls whatever it is. 

Speaker 1  (14:36)
And then you can have a project in GitHub, or whatever, then that puts all those models nice information in there. So then like, if you happen to have to recover, you at least have a point in time. 

Speaker 2  (14:48)
That's one of the things with I. I'm always open to adapting or changing if there's a better option right? Even though I've put a lot of work into ChatGPT and building out these agents and these experts If Claude is what makes better sense. 

Speaker 2  (15:10)
Yeah, it's 

Speaker 1  (15:11)
It's what works for you. Sure, if you want, if you want to select, if you took select, you're able to take your Zach GT P right, your model. And you say, okay, clock, what can you do from this is what I got going on over here. 

Speaker 1  (15:24)
How can you improve this for me? Yeah, you know, and that's a great way to go about it. And you don't necessarily have to transfer over to whatever AI you ask. 

Speaker 2  (15:31)
Right? Because they can talk to 

Speaker 1  (15:33)
Well, you can take those improvements and you can include them over here on this side and still live in this. But it's another voice of being like, oh hey, by the way, did you think of this? Did you think of that? 

Speaker 1  (15:44)
Yeah, so that's a good way for you to go approaching. And so like I would take almost any of your bots, I call them bots, but agents, or how are you going to call it right and be like, how would you improve this? If you had this? 

Speaker 1  (15:57)
What would changes would you make? And why pros and cons why you know, or you know, and so then and then have that conversation with the new AI or even like here within ChatGPT I bet you you could probably start a new chat and be like, hey. Grab the model that we have for Zach, GPT or whatever, and be like, how would you improve this? 

Speaker 1  (16:17)
You know, don't don't look at the context of that. But just look at the model and tell me, identify things that you think could be improved, you know, pros and cons. 

Speaker 2  (16:27)
It's definitely part of the how I build them out too. You know, so I ask you, how do you improve 

Speaker 1  (16:32)
Right? Fresh out of eyes is what you're really looking for because then that way you'll be able to and I would take it with a grain of salt and be like do I want that or do I don't want that because just because it says this is an improvement, it was like, well is it really an improvement, just because you say it is don't don't fully believe it, you know, trust what paraphrase but also like is that the direction you want it to go, that's the other question is like it may be like this is an improvement well, yeah in your eyes. 

Speaker 1  (16:59)
But that's not the direction I want this to go, so just really take a look at it and be like, is that really something the direction I want to go with this or do I don't want to go with it. 

Speaker 2  (17:08)
The connectivity is the next step for me is really getting into that pure agentic, AI where, for instance, a project could start with chat Zack GPT then go into the marketing strategist, then go into kinsian sites and use that product knowledge to build out something and then even go as far as scheduling posts are helping to build the ads from scratch and then I mean 

Speaker 3  (17:31)
For some ad construction today, it's just more manual. 

Speaker 2  (17:34)
Gratitude, oh no. It's it's pretty much riding all the ads. Yes, the creative with some templates. 

Speaker 2  (17:41)
But that copy up top, and even the call outs. I'm heavily leaning into Kinsey insights for that copy and tactics as well. We have a pretty good idea. 

Speaker 2  (17:52)
What really gets us that conversion in the lead generation 

Speaker 1  (17:58)
Do you analyze your adside? 

Speaker 2  (18:00)
They're out there. Yeah, we ab test, and do you have 

Speaker 1  (18:03)
The AI analyze your information. 

Speaker 2  (18:06)
I do not have AI analyzed my information. That's a really good thought and also it wouldn't be difficult at all for ChatGPT to do that automatically because we use hubspot and it's already ingrained I've had roadblocks with letting AI into hub spot yet. No, I really want to and 

Speaker 1  (18:28)
There's other ways of going about doing it in the 7th Avenue right back so you can copy and paste and be like analyze this information, you know, so I'm not saying that you need to have it directly connected, but I think it's a great way to look at and be like, hey. We've credited this on TikTok. How's it doing? 

Speaker 1  (18:43)
What's my feedback? What's my? You know who's my target audience on this? 

Speaker 1  (18:47)
Who am I hit and who am I? 

Speaker 2  (18:49)
And now that you say that too, it's not always it's sometimes it's Meta's built-in AI that really does do the now that you say that I was just kind of thinking, like kind of yeah, we do actually kind of have that built-in with the meta business. 

Speaker 1  (19:06)
I'd also take the information and beat it into 

Speaker 2  (19:09)
That's a great point too. And I always take Meadow with a grain of salt too. I mean, when we have something working, I don't, I don't usually shift gears, but for instance, a hydraulic door add has been doing pretty well for us. 

Speaker 2  (19:22)
But once it once I see a plateau and add fatigue, which we were starting to see a lot of ad fatigue within. Here's one of the analyze that's analyze it. But one of the ad fatigues I was seeing with the hydraulic door is really hitting Iowa. 

Speaker 2  (19:39)
Illinois, the corn belt, because it thought Kinsey, manufacturing, let's say, but we're like, let's go to the we want aviation, we want bigger doors and yeah, so I took out a lot of the corn belt for this second half of the ad. We got a huge ramp up out. West Alaska has been great for us to Florida. 

Speaker 2  (19:58)
But for not really quoting many doors before this ad, ran, it's really done a really good job for us. Which again? ChatGPT helped a lot with the copywriting and imaging. 

Speaker 2  (20:11)
I'm still when it comes to imaging, it does okay. Have it cleanup images sometimes. But Adobe's AI is actually worse than ChatGPT's imaging AI which is funny. 

Speaker 2  (20:26)
So yeah. 

Speaker 1  (20:27)
But I would have it analyzed, and I didn't even have it to like If you get to the point where it's automated, like I don't know, daily is noise or if weekly is better for you. But you can be like, oh, you know, categorize each ad's deployment and then feedback on how it's performing. Then, that way you could start your work week off and be like, oh man, this one's really kind of plateaued. 

Speaker 1  (20:49)
So maybe we need to do something different, or we want to target this audience group and this one kind of hit it, and so why did it hit that audience group and not the other ones and so trying to figure out, I don't know if you have, I'm sure you have like targeted audiences. And so then, like, seeing how it's working in those targeted audiences Vs not absolute, you're already doing some of this stuff, I'm just gonna, but that's kind of where I would go with it where it's like generating report. 

Speaker 1  (21:18)
And that's one of the things is, you can start your work week off and like, that's or you know what day you decide to do it or however you want to do it, but I think that would be a great Way freedom can continue improving and then having the AI being able to analyze it. Your I don't know you have a mark. You had a marketing bot, right? 

Speaker 1  (21:38)
I thought so. So like that marketing bot then could be able to take that information and help you kind of focus the next ad towards the group you're trying to hit or the one that you're losing ground on and then kind of go from there, then that way you can kind of start analyzing this work. Scrape for this group, this doesn't work great for this group like you're saying you're kind of maybe plateauing with the corn belt Vs not, and so why were we hitting them at the beginning? 

Speaker 1  (22:06)
And now we're not getting them. How is what was going on with those early maps? 

Speaker 2  (22:11)
Generally, I don't like to switch any targeting for a while. 

Speaker 1  (22:17)
Those are your rules, I you know, I'm just giving you A 

Speaker 2  (22:19)
Yeah, no, no, definitely. And the reason the reason I don't is because that face Meta's review stage the learning phase, it's trying to find the audience within your audience. That's going to engage. 

Speaker 2  (22:33)
And so when you make those changes, you really restart every time. So once I go to that point where let's hey, let's analyze it. Maybe I bring it into, like, you say into AI to analyze the ad and who changes should I make now going forward since we've hit that plateau? 

Speaker 2  (22:49)
I know it's really inspiring the other thing I wrote down while you were going over that is like, maybe having it analyzed, maybe a little bit more of the search console in the Google AI overview, because you're really trying to tackle being included in that AI overview and somebody searching a Kinsey planner model. Yeah, so that yeah, those are really great. Great things to consider and they'll be more than considered. 

Speaker 2  (23:13)
I'll come into 

Speaker 1  (23:14)
Yeah, the only other thoughts I would probably tell you. So you had a spreadsheet going on? Sounds like you had quite a few rows in that spreadsheet. 

Speaker 1  (23:25)
Yeah, is that like updated? Like? Is he pulled out from someplace? 

Speaker 1  (23:29)
Or is that something you guys are maintaining? 

Speaker 3  (23:31)
Government 

Speaker 2  (23:32)
In the Subsidy data, it's Either scraped by Jamie, or actually, I think he found, I'm pretty just a down. 

Speaker 3  (23:40)
Less government data, because it's government funds going as Subsidy programs 

Speaker 2  (23:45)
It's definitely published the way we get it into Excel is Jamie's doing, and with the way this python script worked was at first I was trying to get ChatGPT to go to the ewg website, search the name and it just timed out. I was getting blocked by security and so we have the from 20:22 to 20:25 Subsidy data now and these Excel sheets that Match with our hutspot, export and Nessus. Kendall, that's being done right now. 

Speaker 2  (24:16)
Ucc data has provided by aem, and that's how we get that financial data very 2, very similar python scripts, but two different sets of data. So this isn't the only python script that we're utilizing this one's probably the most elaborate. Now we've done some that we're just like miles from Kinsey, instead of you know, going through and doing things manually, which Scott and I used to do, yeah, we used to go line by line. 

Speaker 2  (24:47)
Okay, let's Google their name. Let's look at their satellite imagery. Let's see if we can find them in uc see if we can find them in ewg, there is weeks where two weeks in a row, that's all Scott, and I were doing, we're sweating leads. 

Speaker 2  (25:01)
This did it in like 13 minutes, which is great. I mean, that's what the beauty of python beauty of AI is that it I've had wrote the script for me, without having any python experience. 

Speaker 1  (25:14)
Python's a great tool that spreadsheet is great. I would just maybe go back and ask it, how would you do it? 

Speaker 2  (25:21)
Yeah, that's a good point. And 

Speaker 1  (25:24)
So there's like, that's why I'm not saying it's not, I'm just saying, yeah, there's nothing wrong, that's the great thing about AI is you can ask it and it's not going to be offended. How would you do this different? 

Speaker 2  (25:34)
You know, a year ago, it wrote these scripts and This laugh and then it kind of sat to the side for a little while, but we just revamped these scripts and I had it rewrite it, and it just did so much better of a job than a year ago. So but I like that ask it, how to do this lead vetting better. But I already know the answer to how we automate it. 

Speaker 2  (25:57)
It's just convincing Steve security, Steve to let me in the hub spot with AI. 

Speaker 1  (26:03)
The best thing is like every stock. You know, I'm having some security concerns, and you know, and mention the roadblocks. You have or concerns that you have. 

Speaker 1  (26:15)
Yeah, and be like, you know, this is why we're doing it now, and what can we do to ease some of these security concerns, and to make this process more efficient than what we're doing today? 

Speaker 2  (26:25)
I found a few answers at that AI summit. We went to, and it was a software that was already in place, but it was something there like we probably redevelop it. 

Speaker 3  (26:36)
You have a script set up to pull the data from python into a separate location. So that it would automatically run every so often. Then, you have a sandbox of the data that 

Speaker 2  (26:45)
Topi, that has 

Speaker 3  (26:48)
It's always updated, but so if it blows up worst case, you just reimport the data. 

Speaker 1  (26:53)
Or you can put an mcp in front of it, if it actually wanted to do 

Speaker 2  (26:56)
M CP is a big part of what we talked about. 

Speaker 1  (26:59)
If someone like you could, I mean, I think you could put one in front of a spread sheet, but you could do it sort of in front of a database would probably be a little bit more efficient. I'd have to ask it the question of how it's doing the things, but or you know, you can add some keys to make it more efficient. You don't need a huge structured database. 

Speaker 1  (27:17)
You can even do a simple 9 sequel database to search, and because you can kind of give it the keys you want to search on and that way it doesn't have to be a full-blown relational database. Yeah, yeah. And 

Speaker 2  (27:32)
But it didn't really have spots. Pretty simple to work with even when it comes to exporting, I mean, we could write a script that like you were kind of saying Gary at exports hub spot every week, uploads or imports and the python script. I mean, could price set up and 

Speaker 3  (27:47)
Then, step 2, because I think we already have some mcp stuff on conversation that's just not there yet, but maybe that's your short-term solution. Until we get the real long-term solution 

Speaker 1  (27:57)
Or you even standed up in a doctor container and had the python work against that or had the python included in the Docker container. And when you fire up, the doctor container just runs. That way, you're kind of it's dedicated space, and it's not damaging anything in the process. 

Speaker 2  (28:11)
I think the worry is also how secure is ChatGPT? Because obviously our enterprise says it's not sharing and using our data for other environments, but I think that's the worry still which Stephen I talked about. Read-only 

Speaker 1  (28:28)
Yeah, we haven't. 

Speaker 3  (28:30)
Python's running. 

Speaker 1  (28:31)
It's yeah, python's doing the work for you. So it's not really even GPT doing that work unless you're burning it from within there. But 

Speaker 2  (28:39)
It's ran, and I like this Google collab for running this python script. But the agentic AI process would be getting that hub spot to python, back into hub spot and populating the fields that we would need to populate within hubspot that we can easily go and look through track sales as well registrations. So a win from marketing is when they come into, they're not a Kinsey customer, they come in on a metaphor. 

Speaker 2  (29:09)
On top of the funnel, go through the steps and then get to that sales funnel, and then you know, buy. So that's what we're always trying to look for the fun thing about the hydraulic door is that it's instant. You know, get a quote right? 

Speaker 2  (29:24)
So it's yeah, faster to go to that point. 

Speaker 1  (29:29)
No, I think everything else you had to use is solid. Do anything as like I said, I think just kind of backing up your stuff and then asking some different ais on, hey, I have this model working over here and what do you think of it? Give me your honest feedback and yeah, I think that'll kind of help you like I said, take it all and don't accept them all, but ask yourself, is this the direction I want this particular bot? 

Speaker 2  (29:51)
To go, have you messed with any of the agent? I know. This is kinda new for chat. 

Speaker 2  (29:55)
GPT, but also I need to start using codex a little more for python and stuff like that too. But this looks really interesting on like, if you barrows the templates, it's exactly what I'm wanting out of the lead Gen. See another is one that's already a template for it pretty much But yeah, even like design partner, going to Adobe express and 

Speaker 1  (30:19)
Bring it in down. Well, the other thing is, you can even have it compared to the template too. You can be like, hey, I got this spot, does something similar. 

Speaker 1  (30:27)
What are the differences between this? And what you guys have, and then that will kind of give you an idea. 

Speaker 2  (30:33)
These custom GPT you can't connect them with the the software's the thing I understand about clot. Is that people really like it for like desktop connectivity? It works a little bit better than ChatGPT the way I understand for actually doing processes that are being done on your desktop. 

Speaker 1  (30:54)
Yeah, so I use the CLI OI find it in just a little bit easier for me, but the desktop CLI it's like clock code, but because of there's nothing wrong with what you're working here or if you wanted to do as a desktop a little bit more. Gooey friendly definitely the same questions. I'd be asking and be like, hey, I got this bot or that got this agent. 

Speaker 1  (31:14)
What do you think of it? 

Speaker 2  (31:15)
I am nervous, my world bounces around, right so that I'm going to bounce over to production and video production. But something that would be great for Claude to take over my desktop Emmanuel process. That also, as a time consuming process is we film really high-res raw files, 4K and syncing those files, audio and sometimes it's Hundreds of files as done in there's another software called pluralized, but I've never even thought about purchasing that for doing this sinking, but 

Speaker 1  (31:53)
I would probably suggest a different AI than Claude. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (32:00)
Premiere is probably pretty close to it. 

Speaker 1  (32:02)
I had to do. I'm not familiar with that area. But I do know that it's not the strength of flawed. 

Speaker 1  (32:07)
Yeah, and so I would pick AI would do some marker research and figure out which AI is better in that realm. And then I would go with that 

Speaker 2  (32:16)
Over, I just haven't been impressed with the Adobe's AI services yet. 

Speaker 1  (32:19)
So that's and that's, yeah, it's justified, because I that's not Claude's strength. You can definitely try it. I'm not saying that it wont-work, but I'm just saying you can try it and see if you like it, if you don't like it, then maybe do a bit more research on something else, I do a small sample like if you kind of know. 

Speaker 1  (32:37)
Maybe we want to eat kind of already done and have. This is the this is what I want it to be. And then give it the raw materials again and see how close it gets to what you want, what you have done, then that way, it's a good judgment of did it work did it not work Vs giving it some fresh stuff and you'd be like, huh, okay, but at least you have known quantity. 

Speaker 1  (32:56)
At the end, you can then compare the 2 and I'd probably do it as small as a sample as you feel comfortable giving it. I wouldn't do a major one just because it'd be so hard for you to do the comparison because that's the thing is you have to remember. Is that the person in the loop is the Here's the sticky point. 

Speaker 1  (33:14)
You know because you're the one that has to do the reviewing aspect of so 

Speaker 2  (33:18)
And if it's something already out there that does that work, let's say I had to spend 2 days to figure it out, it would have, you know, pluralizes a $100 a year, then I think Financial wise is better to save my man-hours. Have something that's already in place. I'm big into templates, especially right now, when we're a team of 3, that's going down to 2, how do we streamline? 

Speaker 2  (33:46)
So yeah 

Speaker 1  (33:47)
No, and yeah, you can definitely use clogged to kind of help you streamline stuff, but I don't think there's wrong anything wrong with using ChatGPT to kind of ask if those questions too. Yeah, they're both capable of helping you, you know, along the lines and you can bounce between the 2 and get a solid answer that way too. There's nothing wrong with that. 

Speaker 3  (34:07)
Do you have access to cloudboard? 

Speaker 2  (34:09)
No, I do not. I haven't requested it quite yet. I'm more interested in learning it at the moment. 

Speaker 2  (34:15)
I don't think it will be too much of a learning curve, but I think I'll find uses for it fairly quickly like I've expressed with you Gary, it's hard for me to like, well, how much of this work will translate over to cloud or will I lose some of these? A custom GPT said, I really and it lean into I don't 

Speaker 1  (34:35)
I think you can't lose him. I think it's a little different, but 

Speaker 2  (34:40)
I still get the result. 

Speaker 1  (34:42)
I want that to think that the other thing too is you have. If you had both her a month or 2, then you could really do some comparison and see which one really because I don't my understanding is that you guys aren't picking Claude over everything else is like, you kind of can. 

Speaker 3  (34:57)
It's the undetermined technology. But it sounds like for I'll say, like a base software like chat Vs Claude, where, like, you know, almost every like the standard user will probably end up being more than likely clawed, probably with some exceptions for chat. Because chat is actually arguably better for your use case in terms of the photos and videographies of what I've been told read about Claude, that's kind of its limitations relative to chat. 

Speaker 3  (35:25)
But in the other areas, Claude seems to outperform chat on that kind of one piece, so that's carving wise. 

Speaker 2  (35:30)
Yeah, yeah, for sure. Well. So it's been pretty fun. 

Speaker 2  (35:32)
Making the shirts. 

Speaker 1  (35:34)
I code ax is definitely 

Speaker 3  (35:36)
Not the only one I should say. 

Speaker 1  (35:38)
Yeah, yeah, so yeah, I mean, you can definitely try to make in the change. 

Speaker 2  (35:43)
I'm gonna have a daughter in November there you go. And so yeah, I made a show the ones eat 

Speaker 1  (35:48)
Oh, nice. 

Speaker 2  (35:50)
I don't have one that says emergence. 

Speaker 1  (35:53)
Pretty much. 

Speaker 2  (35:54)
That's the most recent. Yes, baby corn eh with that on it. 

Speaker 1  (36:01)
But yeah, I would bounce a little bit between the 2 and see, but I do think for what you're doing for the work you're doing. I definitely say right now. Chad is probably better than Claude, but I'd also look at a few others that are out there kind of do a little bit of search and be like, hey, what is really good with this? 

Speaker 1  (36:18)
And then what is 

Speaker 3  (36:20)
Is today who knows right tomorrow? 

Speaker 1  (36:22)
You know, and that's the thing is, like, and this is where the backups come into play and like you back up all your agents that you already have, and then as you continue to move from one to the other to the other you know, because yeah, in a year be like, oh we chose to stay with chap and now who bar is out here and Fu bar is the greatest and so we're gonna go ahead and see what that switch looks like we're gonna play with a 2 month window, allow you to evaluate the tool and then decide if that's where you want to go or not. 

Speaker 2  (36:50)
So we'll be interesting to see what other ais will come about. And this is all theory now, and you know, I mean people have favorites when AI, but my theory is that you're already seeing agentic and ChatGPT or OpenAI, they're the Amazon and apple, you know, I don't think they're gonna, I think you'll see one. Maybe take off from the other and maybe even one become obsolete at 1 point, but here I think we're already gonna find pretty quickly. 

Speaker 2  (37:20)
Who the leaders in AI will 

Speaker 1  (37:22)
A compute resources, the biggest thing and right? They're the 2 that have all the compute. Resources tied up. 

Speaker 1  (37:28)
So at some point, somebody's gotta either play ketchup or yeah, that's just where it's going to be. 

Speaker 2  (37:35)
Grok, you know, any use cases with that used grocer. I'm sorry yeah, I get asked him. I use it, but I've never, you know, yeah, I never really dabbled with groc. 

Speaker 2  (37:49)
Now Gemini, I use for personal cooking recipes stuff like that, you know, it's great. 

Speaker 1  (37:56)
Now the Gemini and I we have a tough relationship. It doesn't what I 'm navigating on my phone. And I ask it to call my wife and it goes, do you mean someone like does that sound like the name I just gave you? 

Speaker 2  (38:08)
You should see how short I am with Alexa. Yeah, ask her like I cook a lot, so I'm like, what's the temperature of so-and-so on, it'll give me a whole story. And yeah, just like Alexa, listen I just need an answer. 

Speaker 1  (38:21)
Just so it's like I just or like you'll give it. Give me directions and it'll give you directions to It. But then it continues to talk and I'm like, you realize I'm driving, right, you know. 

Speaker 1  (38:29)
But you know, but it's like, well, be safe and drive. And then, blah blah blah's like, just gotta, you've told it countless times 

Speaker 2  (38:37)
Be careful how I gotta be careful. How short I am with Alexa? In case she takes over the world 1 day, you know 

Speaker 1  (38:45)
So but yeah, I think you're right. I think we're kind of seeing the writing on the wall as far as like where people are going to because I mean, obviously data centers now are like, I think people are wise. The data centers is like you're going to destroy the people's area that they're in. 

Speaker 1  (39:00)
And 

Speaker 2  (39:01)
Yeah, it's been weird so 

Speaker 1  (39:03)
Dude, I can see data data 

Speaker 2  (39:05)
The Utah data center from Mr. Wonderful vinegar, state taxpayers covering it. We were talking about this at lunch. 

Speaker 2  (39:13)
Like, sure, it's going to create construction jobs, road jobs for about 6 months. And then works at a data center, 10 people security guards and 10 people. Yeah, yeah, so yeah. 

Speaker 1  (39:26)
I bring the 10 people from and out-of-state anyway. 

Speaker 2  (39:29)
Put the tech side of things. Yeah, they'll be coming from, yeah, so security guards, they'll be very local guys. 

Speaker 1  (39:37)
Pretty soon that'll be bought. 

Speaker 2  (39:39)
That 2I know would be interesting. But they talked a lot about the multimodal AI at this AI summit, which I thought was really interesting. I have an automated mower 2. 

Speaker 2  (39:49)
So like that's kind of the AI camera, so I think that's kind of cool and you think about use cases for Kinsey, you know, and what Kinsey used to do. And you know. Yeah, well, if you got me, had any generated images sent from Susie to you from me that I'm sorry, I've concepted up and you've had it right out. 

Speaker 2  (40:12)
This might be something to share to you to show you, like how somebody with no expertise in automated vehicles or engineering can really create a fast starting point. Because I'd had it right out everything from a build of materials technology tech stack list. I mean, I wasn't really messed around with it too long. 

Speaker 2  (40:35)
But it was having fun with it. But yeah, maybe I'll send any of those just a reference. But nothing that should really be taken too seriously, just mostly looked at. 

Speaker 2  (40:46)
I think, well you know what I mean, it's almost like it's a thought because everybody that gets on AI, you know what they create with it, it can be fascinating, but I think sometimes for me. Stay on. Stay on a level playing field. 

Speaker 2  (41:04)
Not a playing field level. Keep your head level. I guess you know, like, I'm a marker and a producer. 

Speaker 2  (41:10)
That's really what I need to focus with AI. I can have a little fun. I can send it your way, but you know, there's people here that really could do something cool with automation or any type of thing like that with AI too well. 

Speaker 1  (41:26)
It's all an idea, you know, it's where you take 

Speaker 2  (41:28)
Exactly. 

Speaker 1  (41:29)
That can take the groundwork you laid and then poke holes in it. And bulletproof it later and see where it goes. So 

Speaker 2  (41:35)
Or just to help somebody that hasn't used AI. Let's say in like Engineering, like this is where you kind of start and their minds are gonna have the engineer's mind's going to have a lot more insight on what to tell AI to consider, you know, than I do. 

Speaker 3  (41:52)
Yeah, it was a little problems, but I think that's that's normal. 

Speaker 2  (41:56)
Yeah, that waterfall prompting to I think that's helpful. I like to prompt the prompt so then when I bring it in, it really has a detailed prompt. But you know, with that python script, it's like, well, now we need to change this. 

Speaker 2  (42:08)
You know, like just short prompts to tinker and fine-tune, right? So yeah, took that ewg python script was probably rewritten 5 times until it was perfect. And that's pretty, you know, that's pretty nuts, that's pretty good. 

Speaker 2  (42:24)
Yeah, and you have to give the AI the credit right? So well, sure. Yeah, sure, but, yeah, no, it's been good for me. 

Speaker 2  (42:33)
I know that. 

Speaker 1  (42:35)
And for great, no I think it's solid, like so do anything I'd be concerned about just back up information and always asking, how can I improve and use in other agents to kind of help you? Or other ais, a kind of poke holes in it, sometimes we're even using itself to poke holes in it, and see where it goes. 

Speaker 2  (42:51)
What do you think of copilot? Then, for Microsoft. As I haven't found that one to be too intelligent. 

Speaker 1  (42:58)
And it's great for code assist, but I don't think it's great for anything else. So like I stopped using it probably 7 months ago. 

Speaker 2  (43:07)
I have to find like help my grammar on emails or something like that. But the one Kinsey insights that's on co-pilot is just not as smart as the one I have in ChatGPT. But it's still doing a really good job of referencing the literature. 

Speaker 2  (43:21)
So if you have questions like, how many pounds of downforce is true depth, have it can answer that fast. So somebody says 600? That's where the 150 pounds up, just making sure. 

Speaker 2  (43:32)
Oh, yeah? Oh, yeah, do you know how often I listen I listen to Brad needs then more than anybody in this world. What I want to speak your joke to his wife she ever says I've heard enough that he can say well, he guess 
